<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>ChurchDeploy</title>
 <link href="http://churchdeploy.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://churchdeploy.com/"/>
 <updated>2014-09-25T12:42:51-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://churchdeploy.com</id>
 <author>
   <name>Jonathan Simcoe</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Antiquated</title>
   <link href="http://churchdeploy.com/2014/09/25/antiquated/"/>
   <updated>2014-09-25T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://churchdeploy.com/2014/09/25/antiquated</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/antiquated.svg&quot; alt=&quot;smaller&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the one word I would use to describe Church and technology. This is not as much the case today with large church media outlets like &lt;a href=&quot;http://marshill.com&quot;&gt;Mars Hill&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://lifechurch.tv&quot;&gt;LifeChurch.tv&lt;/a&gt;, and the too-many-to-mention churches doing rich, interactive meaningful communication through technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of Church Deploy is simple: we want to help contribute meaningfully to the technology stack of the Church. We also want to help churches and church staff think carefully about design and how this affects their varied communication channels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mostly, we believe that technology is a gift that we are to steward as Christians. It enables us to reach more people with the Gospel of Jesus Christ. We also believe that design is an opportunity for the creative expression that God designed into the universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The beauty of the world is a communication of God&amp;#39;s beauty.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Jonathan Edwards&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we have the opportunity, we want to make the most of technology, the web, and culture to give reflect God&amp;#39;s beauty back to the world as we seek to steward His gifts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Analog is not bad. In fact, much of the craftsmanship revolution is reverting back to handcrafted goodness. There is a balance to strike between analog and digital. More than than, we need to understand how to use media, how to communicate well, and when to use technology and when to avoid it. All that being said, we hope that we can help contribute to the church not being so &lt;em&gt;antiquated&lt;/em&gt; and our end goal is all to see more people to come to a saving knowledge of Jesus Christ.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
